hi I'm Trevor Noah and I'm South African
and because I'm South African people
from all over the world insist on asking
me questions about South Africa so I
decided to make an ad to answer some of
those fascinating questions like how
cold and snowy is your Christmas well
Tracy unfortunately we can't afford snow
no I'm just playing we're in the
southern hemisphere which means when
it's freezing in Connecticut it's
fantastic fantastic in K Town clouse
sent me this one can you play golf in
South Africa well clouse we actually
have some of the finest golf courses in
the world but judging by your 37
handicap can you play
golf how many stars are your five-star
hotels Brian wants to know can I meet
the Lions well I don't know if you want
to meet them but you can see them on
Safari and get this it's not just lion
Brian we've got everything there's
elephants there's rhinos there's
giraffes there's buffalos there's
leopards come on man expand your
horizons
ostriches is South Africa fun is it fun
are you even watching this commercial
Michelle paragliding bungee jumping
surfing river rafting shockk cage diving
hot air balloons hiking cycling wine
tasting whatever this guy is doing does
that not look like to you Michelle does
that not look like fun so now that I've
shown you South Africa my only question
is when are you coming to experience it
for
yourself